Guide to the Time Inc. Annex Files 1854, 1909, 1923-2014 MS 3009-RG 39
New-York Historical Society
- The March of Time: Movie: Library Sales, 1941-1953, undated (Offsite-box 3931, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Movie: Library Sales [RESTRICTED], 1950-1953 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Library Settlement, 1941-1953, undated (Offsite-box 3931, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Movie: Music: Miscellaneous, 1936-1937, 1950-1951, 1961-1965, undated (Offsite-box 3931, Folder 14)
- The March of Time: Movie: Music: American Society of Composers, Authors, and Publishers (ASCAP) [RESTRICTED], 1951-1953 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Music: Fox, Sam [RESTRICTED], 1950-1951 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Music: Shaindlin, Jack [RESTRICTED], 1950-1951 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Newsreel Pools, 1942-1951, undated (Offsite-box 3931, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Movie: Newsreel Pools [RESTRICTED], 1942 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Newsreel Status, 1935-1943, 1950-1951, undated (Offsite-box 3931, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Movie: Newsreel Status [RESTRICTED], 1943-1947 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Non-Theatrical Films, 1935-1944, undated (Offsite-box 3931, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Movie: Photo Reporter, 1935-1938 (Offsite-box 3931, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Movie: Promotion, 1945-1947, undated (Offsite-box 3931, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Movie: Promotions/Advertisements, 1935-1936, 1938 (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Movie: Promotions/Advertisements, 1935-1936, 1938 (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Movie: Promotions/Advertisements, 1943-1945 (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Movie: Promotions/Advertisements, 1946 (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Movie: Promotions/Advertisements, 1947 (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Movie: Promotions/Advertisements, 1948-1955 (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Movie: Promotions/Advertisements, undated (Offsite-box 4032, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Movie: Promotion Booklets, 1935-1937, 2006, undated (Offsite-box 3931, Folder 20-22)
- The March of Time: Movie: Promotion Reports, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 3931, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Movie: Publicity, 1936, 1942, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 1-2)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Movie: Index, undated (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 3)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Index, Synopses and Continuities, 1981? (Offsite-box 2811, Reel 1-2)
  1 microfilm reel. On label: "March of Time: (Continuities) Roll 1 Volume I to Volume XII, Number 1-6."
  1 microfilm reel. On label: "March of Time: (Continuities) Roll 2 Volume XII Number 7 to Volume XVII Number 1-6, also "Specials"."
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Specials: The Golden Twenties, 1950 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Specials: The Holy Year at the Vatican, 1950 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Specials: If Moscow Strike, 1951 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Specials: The Ramparts We Watch, 1940 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Specials: The Story of the Vatican, 1941 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Specials: We Are the Marines, 1942 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Specials: This is Russia, 1953 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume I Issue 1, 1935 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume I Issue 2, 1935 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume I Issue 3, 1935 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume I Issue 4, 1935 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 14)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume I Issue 5, 1935 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume I Issue 6, 1935 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume I Issue 7, 1935 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume I Issue 8, 1935 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume I Issue 9, 1935 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume II Issue 1, 1936 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 20)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume II Issue 2, 1936 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 21)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume II Issue 3, 1936 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 22)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume II Issue 4, 1936 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume II Issue 5, 1936 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 24)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume II Issue 6, 1936 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 25)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume II Issue 7, 1936 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 26)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume II Issue 8, 1936 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 27)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 1, 1936 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 28)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 2, 1936 (Offsite-box 2796, Folder 29)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 3, 1936 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 1)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 4, 1936 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 2)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 5, 1936 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 3)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 6, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 7, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 8, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 9, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 10, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 11, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 12, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 13, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 14, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume III Issue 15, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 1, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 141)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 2, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 3, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 4, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 5, 1937 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 6, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 7, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 20)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 8, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 21)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 9, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 22)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 10, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 11, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 24)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 12, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 25)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IV Issue 13, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 26)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 1, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 27)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 2, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 28)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 3, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 29)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 4, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 30)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 5, 1938 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 31)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 6, 1939 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 32)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 7, 1939 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 33)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 8, 1939 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 34)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 9, 1939 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 35)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 10, 1939 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 36)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 11, 1939 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 37)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 12, 1939 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 38)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume V Issue 13, 1939 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 39)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 11, 1939 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 40)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 2, 1939 (Offsite-box 2791, Folder 41)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 3, 1939 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 1)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 4, 1939 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 2)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 5, 1939 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 3)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 6, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 7, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 8, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 9, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 10, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 11, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 12, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VI Issue 13, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 1, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 2, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 3, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 14)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 4, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 5, 1940 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 6, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 7, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 8, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 9, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 20)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 10, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 21)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 11, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 22)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 12, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VII Issue 13, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 24)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 1, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 25)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 2, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 26)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 3, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 27)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 4, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 28)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 5, 1941 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 29)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 6, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 30)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 7, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 31)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 8, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 32)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 9, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 33)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 10, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 34)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 11, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 35)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 12, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 36)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume VIII Issue 13, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 37)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 1, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 38)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 2, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 39)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 3, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 40)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 4, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 41)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 5, 1942 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 42)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 6, 1943 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 43)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 7, 1943 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 44)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 8, 1943 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 45)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 9, 1943 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 46)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 10, 1943 (Offsite-box 2792, Folder 47)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 11, 1943 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 1)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 12, 1943 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 2)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume IX Issue 13, 1943 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 3)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 1, 1943 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 2, 1943 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 3, 1943 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 4, 1943 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 5, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 6, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 7, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 8, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 9, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 10, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 11, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 14)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 12, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume X Issue 13, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 1, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 2, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 3, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 4, 1944 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 20)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 5, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 21)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 6, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 22)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 7, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 8, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 24)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 9, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 25)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 10, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 26)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 11, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 27)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 12, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 28)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XI Issue 13, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 29)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XII Issue 1+2, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 30)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XII Issue 3+4, 1945 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 31)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XII Issue 5+6, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 32)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XII Issue 7+8, 1946 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 33)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XII Issue 9+10, 1946 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 34)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XII Issue 11+12, 1946 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 35)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XII Issue 13, 1946 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 36)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIII Issue 1+2, 1946 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 37)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIII Issue 3+4, 1946 (Offsite-box 2793, Folder 38)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIII Issue 5+6, 1946-1947 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 1)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIII Issue 7+8, 1947 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 2)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIII Issue 9+10, 1947 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 3)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIII Issue 11+12, 1947 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIII Issue 13, 1947 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIV Issue 1+2, 1947 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIV Issue 3+4, 1947 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIV Issue 5+6, 1947-1948 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIV Issue 7+8, 1948 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIV Issue 9+10, 1948 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIV Issue 11+12, 1948 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIV Issue 13-15, 1948 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XIV Issue 16-18, 1948 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XV Issue 1+2, 1949 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 14)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XV Issue 3+4, 1949 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 15)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XV Issue 5+6, 1949 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XV Issue 7+8, 1949 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XV Issue 9+10, 1949 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XV Issue 11+12, 1949 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XVI Issue 1+2, 1950 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 20)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XVI Issue 3+4, 1950 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 21)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XVI Issue 5+6, 1950 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 22)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XVI Issue 7+8, 1950 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XVII Issue 1+2, 1951 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 24)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XVII Issue 3+4, 1951 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 25)
- The March of Time: Movie: Scripts: Volume XVII Issue 5+6, 1951 (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 26)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Basic English, 1944-1954, undated (Offsite-box 2794, Folder 27)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Basic English [RESTRICTED], 1944-1945 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Battlefields of the Pacific, 1941-1942 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 1)
  Nitrate film was removed during processing and not retained due to deterioration
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Golden Twenties: Dope Sheets, undated (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 2-3)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Golden Twenties: Promotion and Publicity, 1950, undated (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 4)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Golden Twenties: Legal Releases, 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 5)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Golden Twenties: Legal: Releases [RESTRICTED], 1948-1950 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Golden Twenties: Miscellaneous, 1948-1950 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 6)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Golden Twenties: Legal: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1948-1952 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Bush and Bust Trust, 1944-1951, undated (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 7)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Bush and Bus Trust [RESTRICTED], 1950 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Contracts [RESTRICTED], 1952-1954 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Continuities, undated (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 8)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: General Electric (GE), 1949-1954 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 9)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: General Electric [RESTRICTED] (GE) [RESTRICTED], 1950-1952 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Legal: Music License, Releases, etc. [RESTRICTED], 1950-1952 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Outside Library [RESTRICTED], 1950 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Goodman and Kaufman Favorite Films, 1952-1953 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 10)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Goodman and Kaufman Favorite Films [RESTRICTED], 1952 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Outside Library, 1950-1951, undated (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 11)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Promotion and Publicity, 1951 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 12)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: If Moscow Strikes: Miscellaneous, 1949-1954 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 13)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch [RESTRICTED], 1939-1940, 1951 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Baptism of Fire, 1940-1941 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 14-15)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Baptism of Fire, 1940 (Offsite-box 3264, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Baptism of Fire [RESTRICTED], 1940, 1952 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Continuities, 1940-1941 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 16)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Distribution [RESTRICTED], 1931-1942 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Financial, 1939-1940 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 17)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Foreign, 1940-1942 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 18)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Foreign [RESTRICTED], 1940 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Legal: Releases [RESTRICTED], 1939 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Legal: Release Slips [RESTRICTED], 1940 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Legal: Release Slips [RESTRICTED], 1940 (Offsite-box R73)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Music [RESTRICTED], 1940 (Offsite-box R72)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Music, 1940, undated (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 19)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Promotion, 1940, undated (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 20-21)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Promotion, undated (Offsite-box 4045, Folder 1)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Response, 1940 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 22)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Miscellaneous, 1939-1941, 1951 (Offsite-box 2795, Folder 23)
- The March of Time: Movie: Specials: Ramparts We Watch: Miscellaneous [RESTRICTED], 1939 (Offsite-box R73)